<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>The Fun Corner</title><link>https://adelinewei.github.io/</link><description>This is my cool site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 16:24:15 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adelinewei.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Summer 2023</title><link>https://adelinewei.github.io/posts/summer-2023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 16:24:15 +0200</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://adelinewei.github.io/posts/summer-2023/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m not the biggest fan of Swedish summers, with the sun shining relentlessly day and night. The constant brightness can make it hard to find a moment of peace in my mind. However, this year, I challenged myself to make the most of the summer by trying out different activities.
Going SUP (Stand-Up Paddle) at the Lake I must admit, I fell in love with paddleboarding at the lake. Whether sitting or standing on the board, the gentle rocking motion caused by the waves and the soothing sound of the paddle slicing into the water had a truly relaxing effect on me.</description></item><item><title>Introduction and Demonstration to Git Rebase</title><link>https://adelinewei.github.io/posts/git-rebase/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:48:00 +0200</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://adelinewei.github.io/posts/git-rebase/</guid><description>Git rebase is a powerful command that lets us reapply commits on top of another commit or branch. It is a very useful command for both collaborating with others and developing our own project. We all know it is a good practice to keep a commit within reasonable size and readable for either code review or for later reference. However, as a developer myself, I often make mistakes when I am too focus on the coding flow to pay attention to follow displine.</description></item></channel></rss>